All right so let's start with the dos and don'ts of giving a presentation.
好的，让我们从演示文稿的注意事项开始。
Now most presentations have what's called a.
现在大多数演示文稿都有所谓的 a。
That's actually called a slide show but it's often called a PowerPoint.
这实际上称为幻灯片放映，但通常称为 PowerPoint。
It's often abbreviated as PBT.
它通常缩写为 PBT。
Let's just call it a PowerPoint or a PPD.
我们就称它为 PowerPoint 或 PPD。
In this lesson even though that's actually not the real name.
在本课中，即使这实际上不是真名。
But anyway the dos and don'ts things we should do things we should avoid.
但无论如何，我们应该做的事情和不应该做的事情，我们应该避免的事情。
Let's start with the don'ts.
让我们从不要做的开始。
Well you don't want to write too much on the PPD.
好吧，您不想在 PPD 上写太多。
If you write a lot on the PPE it's going to actually have less of an impact.
如果你在 PPE 上写了很多，实际上影响会更小。
Now I'm writing a lot here but that's because you're coming along with me for each thing that I'm writing.
现在我在这里写了很多，但那是因为你陪我一起写我写的每一件事。
You're sort of seeing me write most of it down.
你好像看到我把大部分内容都写下来了。
So we're kind of exploring this space together.
所以我们正在一起探索这个空间。
But when you write a lot on each slide when you write a lot on each slide it actually makes the audience
但是当你在每张幻灯片上写很多东西 当你在每张幻灯片上写很多东西时，它实际上会让观众
go like that.
就那样去吧。
But if you just have a few key things very key important key means important things on the slide and
但是如果你只有几个关键的东西 非常关键 重要的关键意味着幻灯片上的重要东西
it's very easy to read and takes three seconds to read.
它非常容易阅读，只需三秒钟即可阅读。
Then it's going to have much more impact and your ideas which you're explaining can then focus on those
然后它会产生更大的影响，然后你正在解释的想法可以专注于那些
points and you can have a visual reference to the things you're talking about.
点，你可以对你正在谈论的事情有一个视觉参考。
That's actually what the PBT is usually for the words coming out of your mouth.
这实际上就是 PBT 通常用于从你嘴里说出来的话。
Those are the details.
这些是细节。
That's the explanation.
这就是解释。
Then the thing on the slide that's the the reference point.
然后幻灯片上的东西就是参考点。
That's the thing that keeps you focused on what's the topic again.
这就是让你再次专注于主题的东西。
OK.
好的。
So remember the role of of that and also don't read it too much from the PBT maybe a little bit is OK.
所以记住它的作用，也不要从 PBT 中读太多，也许一点点就可以了。
Sure.
当然。
But if you just turn around and say and in 1997 we had a blah blah blah blah blah and you read what
但如果你转身说，在 1997 年，我们有一个废话，废话，你读到了什么
it says.
它说。
That is a mistake generally speaking because you're dis connecting with the audience the audience the
一般而言，这是一个错误，因为您与观众断开了联系
people you're talking to by turning around and because you're reading it's now much less engaging.
通过转身与您交谈的人，并且因为您正在阅读它现在变得不那么吸引人了。
If for example I was reading a script for this course looking over there you could tell.
例如，如果我正在阅读本课程的脚本，你可以看出来。
And it would feel less engaging for you.
它会让你感觉不那么吸引人。
You would be less interested.
你会不太感兴趣。
So be very careful about that.
所以要非常小心。
You want to avoid reading too much and you certainly want to avoid turning around too much to actually
你想避免阅读太多，你当然想避免过多地转身去实际
face away from your audience.
远离你的观众。
Hey don't memorize every word do not memorize every word.
嘿不要记住每一个单词不要记住每一个单词。
For some reason a lot of people who do presentations feel like they have to memorize every word.
出于某种原因，很多做演讲的人觉得他们必须记住每一个单词。
If you do that it's not a presentation.
如果你这样做，它就不是一个演示文稿。
It's called a speech.
这叫演讲。
A speech is something that has to be so perfectly worded because you're the president or something or
演讲是必须措辞完美的东西，因为你是总统什么的，或者
a king that you can't make any mistakes and so you read it or you memorize it and say it when you're
一个你不会犯任何错误的国王，所以你读它或者你记住它，当你犯错时说出来
talking to people.
与人交谈。
If you are memorizing every word it's basically the same as sitting there and reading in front of everybody.
如果你要记住每一个单词，那基本上和坐在那里在每个人面前阅读是一样的。
In 1997 there was a terrible flood and it's not quite that serious but that's the idea.
1997 年发生了一场可怕的洪水，虽然没有那么严重，但就是这样。
People can tell but if you have clear points in your mind and you know what you're talking about.
人们可以分辨出来，但如果你有明确的想法并且你知道你在说什么。
But you don't have maybe all of the exact words then it feels natural.
但是您可能没有所有确切的单词，然后感觉很自然。
It feels like real human communication which hopefully this feels like and I'm not planning every single
感觉就像真正的人类交流，希望这种感觉就像我并没有计划每一个
word that I'm saying I'm speaking about a topic that I know about.
我所说的词我正在谈论一个我知道的话题。
And watch TED talks if you haven't already I'm sure you have but.
如果您还没有，请观看 TED 演讲，我确定您已经看过了。
But Ted is Ted dot com.
但 Ted 是 Ted dot com。
There are many many great TED Talks and 95 percent of the great ones are not memorized.
有很多很棒的 TED 演讲，而 95% 的精彩演讲都没有被记住。
They're speaking about some points.
他们在谈论一些观点。
OK.
好的。
So avoid memorizing every word don't read.
所以避免记住每一个不读的单词。
Must you really have to.
你真的必须这样做。
And don't write too much on your teeth.
并且不要在牙齿上写太多。
All right.
好的。
Things you should do.
你应该做的事情。
Number one.
第一。
Be yourself.
做你自己。
Obviously if you try to make a fake personality when you're standing up in front of people Hello everyone
很明显，当你站在人们面前时，如果你试图做出一个假人，大家好
or or whatever people can feel it OK just be yourself be natural.
或者或者任何人们觉得可以的东西，做你自己自然就好。
Speak as you speak.
一边说话一边说话。
OK.
好的。
Speak to the audience.
对观众讲话。
Now this is kind of related to this one but no who is listening to you speak.
现在这有点与这个有关，但没有谁在听你说话。
If you're giving a presentation and there are a hundred thousand not too many say one hundred thousand
如果您要进行演示，并且有十万而不是太多，请说十万
two thousand people two hundred people ten people four people.
两千人两百人十人四人。
Your presentation is going to be different if it's for people.
如果是针对人的，您的演示文稿将会有所不同。
Are you going to come out and say hello everyone.
你要出来和大家打个招呼吗？
No he won't do so.
不，他不会那样做。
OK.
好的。
Four people up here.
上面四个人。
I'm glad you came.
非常高兴你来了。
Why don't we sit at a table together and I'll talk through my points and then we can discuss OK.
我们为什么不一起坐在一张桌子旁，我会讨论我的观点，然后我们可以讨论好。
Or maybe you come out and it's a bunch of teenagers in high school.
或者，也许你出来时是一群高中生。
Well then you're going to speak differently.
那你就换个方式说话。
Know who you're talking to know your audience and speak to them.
知道你在说谁，了解你的听众并与他们交谈。
So every presentation will probably not be the same.
因此，每个演示文稿可能都不相同。
Different sizes of audiences different groups of people.
不同规模的观众不同的人群。
OK so you have to think about that when you come out.
好的，所以当你出来的时候你必须考虑一下。
When you start talking you really do speak to that specific group of people.
当你开始说话时，你真的是在和那群特定的人说话。
OK.
好的。
Next engage.
接下来搞。
Now this is obvious.
现在这很明显。
This means you need to connect with people.
这意味着您需要与人建立联系。
But if you just start talking and they have no reason the audience the people watching you they have
但是如果你刚开始说话而他们没有理由观看你的观众他们有
no reason to care.
没有理由关心。
You don't give them a reason to care at the beginning especially then you've lost them for 15 minutes
一开始你没有给他们一个关心的理由，尤其是在你失去他们 15 分钟之后
or however long your presentation is engage.
或者无论您的演示文稿有多长。
Use a hook at the beginning.
在开始时使用钩子。
Find a way to make them care about you and your topic right at the beginning.
找到一种方法让他们从一开始就关心你和你的话题。
Right when you start and if you do that then you're going to carry them along with you.
就在您开始时，如果您这样做，那么您将随身携带它们。
And again if you go to Ted and watch TED talks you will see the good ones have something at the beginning
再说一次，如果你去 Ted 看 TED 演讲，你会发现好的演讲一开始就有一些东西
that hooks you grabs you like a fish and you want to listen.
像鱼一样抓住你的钩子，你想听。
This is so interesting why do I care about this.
这太有趣了，我为什么要关心这个。
I don't usually care about this topic but I care about it in this presentation.
我通常不关心这个话题，但我在这个演示文稿中关心它。
Why.
为什么。
Probably because there was a good hook at the beginning.
可能是因为一开始有一个很好的钩子。